Guide to the Mack Buckley Swearingen papers,1920-1969.
Swearingen, Mack Buckley papers, 1920-1969.
- Series I. General Files
  - Red Suspenders over Georgia, 1941 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous, 1955-1957 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Ideas, etc., 1955-1967 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - "Me on Me" read to Elmira College Workshop, 1958-1960 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Sunday Telegram, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - JFK - WECW, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Curiosa, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - The Future of History, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - So You've Come to College, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Honors Speech - Version I, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - The Challenge of Education - Honors Day, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - This is the Way it Was (On Leaving Painsville), 1968 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - The Dodd I Knew, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - History 304 - 20th Century South, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Apologia (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - General Studies Paper (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Wars (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - CC - Misc. Quotations (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Report on the Syracuse Workshop Weekend (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - On the Faculty Inspection of Administrative Operations (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - On Peace and War (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Examination Questions, Misc. (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Barnes Paper - Notes (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Murray and Integration - A Summary of Events at Elmira College (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Term Paper and Instructions (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - MBS - Writings and Publications (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - MBS Vitae (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Thesis - A Few, for Nailing on a Door (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Birth Records - MBS (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Conant's Book - The Education of American Teachers (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - The South and Civil Rights (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - The Old South (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Turkey Journal 2-8, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Turkey Journal Unit 5, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Turkey Journal 7 (8), 1955 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Turkey Journal 9-14, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Turkey Journal 15-20, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Turkey Journal 21-25, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Turkey Journal 26-28, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - Turkey Journal 29-36 (37), 1956 (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - Turkey Journal 4th set, lots missing, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - Turkey Journal 3rd set, lots missing, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - Turkey - Few Units of Diary - 2nd Journey, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - "Arsenic and Old Lace" play Ankara, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - Chapter II - What Makes a Turk? (The Dome of Holy Wisdom) (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - The Dome of Holy Wisdom - Ch. 3 (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - The Dome of Holy Wisdom - Ch. IV, A Clear View of Life (Box 20, Folder 63)
  - The Dome of Holy Wisdom - Ch. IV (Box 20, Folder 64)
  - The Dome of Holy Wisdom - CH. V (Box 20, Folder 65)
  - The Dome of Holy Wisdom - Ch. VI - carbon (Box 20, Folder 66)
  - The Dome of Holy Wisdom - Ch. VII - Suburbia Moves to Asia Minor (Box 20, Folder 67)
  - The Dome of Holy Wisdom - CH. IX (Box 20, Folder 68)
  - The Dome of Holy Wisdom - Ch. IX - The Young Idea (Box 20, Folder 69)
  - The Dome of Holy Wisdom - Ch. 00 (Box 20, Folder 70)
  - The Dome of Holy Wisdom - carbons (Box 20, Folder 71)
  - Revision Text - Contemporary Georgia - The Trust (Box 20, Folder 72)
  - Revision Text - Contemporary Georgia - The Government and Politics (Box 20, Folder 73)
  - Revision Text - Contemporary Georgia - The Early National Period, The Golden Age (Box 20, Folder 74)
  - Revision Text - Contemporary Georgia - The Revolution, The Second Revolution (Box 20, Folder 75)
  - The Whole Person - Act I, 1954 (Box 20, Folder 76)
  - The Whole Person - Act II, Scene 1, 1954 (Box 20, Folder 77)
  - The Whole Person - Act II, Scene 2, 1954 (Box 20, Folder 78)
  - The Whole Person - Act III, 1954 (Box 20, Folder 79)
  - WECW - News in Depth - No. 1 Folder, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 80)
  - WECW - News in Depth - No. 2 Folder, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 81)
  - WECW - News in Depth - No. 3 Folder, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 82)
  - WECW - News in Depth - No. 4 Folder, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 83)
  - WECW - News in Depth - No. 4 Folder, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 84)
  - WECW - News in Depth - No. 5 Folder Broadcasts 22-26, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 85)
  - Broadcast Scripts - Extra Set Incomplete, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 86)
  - Broadcast Scripts - Series II, 1962-1963 (Box 20, Folder 87)
  - Broadcasts - carbon copies, 1963-1964 (Box 20, Folder 88)
  - Broadcasts - Numbers 1-22 carbons, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 89)
  - Broadcasts 1-19, 1965-1966 (Box 20, Folder 90)
  - Certificate of Registration (Oxford), 1926 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Passport, 1924 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Passport, 1926 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Passport, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Glass Slide (broadside) "Avoid Conscription", 1862 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Broadside, 1862 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Broadside, 1930 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Photographs from Turkey Journal, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Photographs from Turkey Journal, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Post Cards, Jackson, Miss. (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Antoine's - Antoine's Annex, New Orleans (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Directory of Americans at Oxford, 1924 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - The Early Life of George Poindexter (MBS), 1934 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Thirty Years of a Mississippi Plantation: Charles Whitmore of Montpelier (MBS), 1935 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Contemporary Georgia Unit IX (MBS), 1942 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Manual for Social Science 101 and 102, 1943-1945 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - The American Oxonian, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Letter from the Postmaster General, 1825 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Road - Homochitto Swamp, report of committee, Louisiana, 1868 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Petition of Joseph Vidal, of Miss, 1838 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Report of the Joint Committee of the General Assembly of Louisiana, 1868 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Handbook of the State of Mississippi, 1885 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Old and New Natchez, 1897 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - The Development of Methodism in the Old Southwest, 1933 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - The American Revolution - an Interpretation, 1852 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Consolidated Debt of the City of New Orleans, 1852 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - 19th Century Political Cartoons (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Colton's Map of the City of New Orleans, 1861 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Map of Mississippi, 1828 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Map of Italy, R. Huger Elliot, 1897 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Diploma, Jackson High School, 1918 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Diploma, Millsaps College (B.A.), 1922 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Diploma, University of Chicago (M.A.), 1923 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Certificate, Kit Kat Chapter of Sigma Upsilon Fraternity, 1920 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Preliminary Sketch of MBS for portrait by Kay Harris (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - Mack to Mother, 1924-1927 (Box 25)
  - Unidentified portrait painting on newspaper, Undated (Folder 1)
- Series II. Flannery O'Connor Correspondence
  - Introducing himself; has been told that she had been in one of his classes at the Women's College of Georgia and wonders if she remembers him, 1962 (Box 23)
  - Replies that she remembers him, but wasn't in his classes; discussed the Women's College, her illness, 1962 (Box 23)
  - MBS to F O'C - would like her to speak at EC, 1962 (Box 23)
  - To MBS - would like to come, but cannot because of difficulties of changing planes, 1962 (Box 23)
  - To F O'C - understands why she cannot come; comments on Granville Hicks' account of his visit to her [ Saturday Review, May 12, 1962 ] Hicks' article clipped from SR (Box 23)
  - To MBS Hicks' piece not the worst; her peacock raising gives her "unnecessary attention", 1962 (Box 23)
  - To MBS religion in the South, 1962 (Box 23)
  - To F O'C religion in the South, 1962 (Box 23)
  - To MBS same subject; why South is a good place for Catholic literature, 1962 (Box 23)
  - To F O'C continuation of subject, 1962 (Box 23)
  - To MBS same, 1963 (Box 23)
  - Richard Poirier's Review of Everything That Rises Must Converge, NYT Book Review, 1965 (Box 23)
- Series III. Eudora Welty Correspondence
  Unless otherwise noted, this correspondence is concerned with arrangements for Miss Welty to speak at Elmira College in the Spring of 1966
  - To MBS Jackson, Miss., Sept. 8, 1962 (Box 23)
  - To EW, Mar. 5, 1963 (Box 23)
  - To MBS, Mar. 18, 1963 (Box 23)
  - To EW, Apr. 23, 1963 (Box 23)
  - To EW Refers to having read an essay by EW in the Atlantic, Oct. 22, 1965 (Box 23)
  - To MBS, Nov. 1, 1965 (Box 23)
  - To EW, Nov. 4, 1965 (Box 23)
  - Malcom Marsden, Professor of English, to EW, Dec. 17, 1965 (Box 23)
  - MM to Curtis L. Barnes, Director of Public Relations, Jan. 18, 1966 (Box 23)
  - EW to MBS Enclosed obituary of Miss Welty's mother, Feb. 10, 1966 (Box 23)
  - MBS to EW, Feb. 15, 1966 (Box 23)
  - [Marsden] to EW, Feb. 21, 1966 (Box 23)
  - EW to MBS and Mary Louise, Mar. 23, 1966 (Box 23)
  - MBS to EW, Apr. 15, 1966 (Box 23)
  - EW to MBS re: his recent visit to Jackson (Box 23)
  - Also, page from the Millsaps College Alumni News Summer "Eudora Welty Named Writer-in-Residence", 1964 (Box 23)
- Series IV. Audiotapes
  - "News in Depth", Dec. 6, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - "Constancy of Change", Mar. 15, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - "News in Depth", Mar. 16, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Unmarked (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - "News in Depth", Nov. 8, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - "News in Depth", Mar. 30, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - "News in Depth" (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - "Conference: The Honor System", Dec. 2, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - "Conference: The Honor System" 2 of 2 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Unmarked, Nov. 1, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - "News in Depth", Dec. 13, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - "News in Depth", Nov. 15, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Unmarked (Box 24, Folder 13-15)